We were consumed by bloodlust.
The Shandora warriors, they only
attacked God's Island Upper Yard,
because they wanted to regain a homeland
of their ancestors which we took.
My lord, you're not thinking
about that again, are you?
Look around.
Look at the peaceful existence
of the citizens of Skypiea.
It wouldn't be this way
had our ancestors not
taken control of the
Upper Yard 400 years ago.
And it is our duty to carry on this battle
to ensure the peaceful
nature of this nation.
We've tried to negotiate with them, but if
they cannot abide by these negotiations,
they do not deserve your compassion.
400 years
I think that it's time for this endless
strife and bloodshed to come to an end.
I only wish that we could
all live in harmony.
Put these needless battles behind us.
Enemy attack!
Is it another attack by the Shandians?
It's not them.
What do you mean?
It's a man who calls himself God Eneru.
What God Eneru?
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the courage
that sail and believe.
And we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow?
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons.
Sailed toward different
dreams, things had changed now!
For together we found, we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious points our destiny!
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me.
Bon voyage, we can't stop all
our troubles, forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there!
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried only helps.
Our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
I want you to stay and take
care of these two, Sue.
Because there's something
important I have to do.
I have to warn them.
No matter what it takes, I won't
let your death be in vain, father.
Sue Sue!
I can't just sit here and cry.
Here!
Hey!
I think this house belongs
to that pretty lady.
The one who plays her harp
on the beach all the time.
Yeah, you're right.
This is her house, for sure.
Her name's Conis, and she
lives here with her dad, Page.
They both seem like really nice people.
They even invited me over
to have lunch one time.
I heard that girl and her
dad are really bad people.
Stay away, or you'll get in trouble.
My mom told me that, too.
She said they were helping
the Blue Sea people.
That can't be.
I swear it's true, they're trouble.
My father said he'd ground me if
he caught me anywhere near them!
Your father said that?
I see
Oh, I'm sorry, I just
remembered your father is.
My daddy's a member of the Enforcers!
And he's out on patrol.
My mom says he'll be coming home soon!
And I can hardly wait!
Because I've never even seen his face.
Oh man, I think it is so awesome!
Your dad is one of the
divine warriors and I'm
sure your dad will come
home to see you real soon.
Skypeel will be dropped back
into the blue sea world.
I can't let his death be in vain!
I must tell the others!
I have to warn them!
What just happened?
Why did all these ruins
fall out of the sky?
Swordsman!
This is not my day!
Don't tell me you fell
down here with all of this!
Yeah, I did!
And it almost killed me!
I'm amazed it didn't.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, good to see you, Robin.
Where am I?
What is this place?
It's the city of gold
we've been looking for.
Did you find the treasure?
I didn't.
There's no evidence
that gold was ever here.
Wow, that was one crazy
ride if I do say so myself.
I think I want to go again.
Are you stupid?
Why in the world did you
hold on to the Waver's jet?
Sorry.
Everyone else managed to escape,
and we've been left behind
because of your stupidity.
It's all your fault.
Don't worry.
Get us out of here.
I've got an idea.
Why don't we make our way down to the back
of the snake and escape out its butthole?
Ah! Think again, jerk!
That's not gonna happen!
Look, it's the horse!
That's a bird!
Thanks, Mr. Weirdo.
We just got lucky when we
landed on these clouds.
We left Luthi and Isa behind.
I hope they're okay.
Pierre's gone to fetch our friends.
And when Push comes to shove, he's
a very reliable bird or horse.
Hey, where did we end up?
What is this place?
Well, to be perfectly honest,
I have no idea where we are,
but it looks like we fell to the clouds.
Thank you very much.
I've traveled all across the
upper yard in my lifetime,
but I've never seen this place before.
Could it be?
Is this really our homeland?
Light the fire of Shandora, in the
name of the great warrior Kolkata!
Light the fire of Shandora!
We're going back to our homeland!
I finally found what
I've been looking for.
The proud city that my
ancestors protected.
Shandora.
I think the snake is
looking for something.
Either that or Luffy's doing
something that's bothering it.
That snake sure is acting strangely.
I think it's crying.
What's the meaning of
this ridiculous outburst?
Just what are you getting
yourself so worked up about?
You've always been an annoyance to me.
And no longer.
Tell Thor.
My son! Oh, no, Nami! She's dead!
There's no way she could
have survived that!
Robin? And Zoro?
When did you guys get here?
Wait!
What are you doing there?
How'd you get out of the snake's stomach?
Glad to see you're all right, Navigator?
Yeah, I think I'm all right.
But I'm not so sure about the others.
Luffy was still in there.
What was he doing in there?
I tried to get him out
but he fell off the waver.
Ah, that brat is nothing
but a pain in the ass.
Is he aware of how much of a hassle he is?
How am I supposed to know?
Just one hit.
That's all it took.
Enaru You destroyed him when my bazooka
couldn't even scratch the snake.
And Aissa, I can only
hope she somehow survived.
Ball cloud.
And a rule.
That's no way to treat your host,
now, is it, Shandorin warrior?
I thought that you'd be happy.
After all, it was I who brought you
here and returned you to your homeland.
Don't get so worked up.
It's time for that later.
This is the beginning.
You don't want the fun
to win so soon, do you?
This is a game to you?
Yes, and a truly petty game at that.
For all of you, we'll be competing
against each other for my entertainment.
Well done.
I'm happy so many of
you've made it this far.
I extend my welcome to you survivors.
And now the fun truly begins.
This is a survival game to see
how many people out of an original
People 81, including myself, are still
standing after three hours on this island.
The last person left will,
of course, be the winner.
Among you are a few participants
who entered late into the game,
but I've decided to allow them to stay.
It will make it all the more interesting.
Now the five of us will continue
on in the final stage of the game.
Did he say five people?
Zoro, Robin, Gunfall,
Bazooka Man, and Eneru.
That's exactly five people.
Good thing he hasn't
noticed that I'm here.
In just a few minutes, the
three hours will be up.
Which means that the six people we
have present here are one too many.
He knows I'm here!
The one thing I know is that
God's prophecy will never falter,
because he is absolute.
I'm curious to see how this
person is going to die.
Will you all fight each other?
Will you gang up on
one of the weaker ones?
Of course.
You could all resist your
fates and force me to pick.
What do you want to do, Robin?
I'm not going to kill
anyone. I won't either.
I won't compete in your sick game.
And I, too, refuse to take part.
Why do you gotta drag me into this?
You're the only one dying today!
Insolent fools!
You dare to threaten me?
Whoa!
This guy's dangerous!
I must admit, I'm quite impressed.
But you have no idea
what you're up against.
Even the four of you together
don't stand a chance against me.
You cannot comprehend the extent of my
powers and what I'm truly capable of.
Look at you, an elderly
buffoon wanting peace.
a warrior who single-mindedly
seeks his homeland,
and thieves from the Blue Sea who
are only concerned with treasures.
All of you, for one reason or another,
seek to save this wretched
place called Skypier.
But you cannot, because this
nation is fundamentally flawed.
I refuse to stand here and
listen to such nonsense.
Now tell me where the divine warriors are!
And what exactly is your goal here today?
Why an ascension, my old
friend? What do you mean?
I mean, when I ascend, I will
return to my rightful place.
What's that?
Are you saying that
you're leaving, Skypiea?
That's right.
I will soon leave this dreadful wasteland.
On the island where I grew up, there were
legends of a place regarded as God's home.
As God's home?
People call this place Endless Birth,
and there, the ground extends as far
as the eye can see, in all directions!
It's my dream to find
this place, this paradise!
Endless Birth, a home fit for a god!
My time spent here battling
over the inconsequential lands
of the Upper Yard has been
nothing but a petty triviality.
Listen to me.
I tell you this place that
you cherish is an abomination.
Consider this.
It was born in the sky,
though it's not a cloud.
It lives in the sky,
though it's not a bird.
This nation which exists in the
sky is an utterly unnatural one.
When we die, we all return
to the earth, to the soil.
But here, there is none.
What exactly are you getting at?
You really shouldn't be
surprised by my intentions.
As God, I'm bound to adhere to
the divine province on nature.
That's why this unnatural nation will
be ripped apart and pulled from the sky.
You're planning on wiping
out Skypea completely?
It's only natural.
Don't be so conceited.
The term god is just the title used
to refer to the leader of this nature.
True, but that will soon change.
A true god does not
live amongst the humans
like you do and treat
them as his playthings.
Former God, Gonefall.
You're worried about the
divine warriors, are you not?
Six years ago,
your divine warriors lost
a battle against my forces,
and I took 650 of your
subordinates under my charge.
They served me well until this morning,
when I could find no more use for them.
I told you, did I not?
The six of us here now are the only
ones left alive in this forsaken place.
Such a shame.
You monster.
It's not that I wanted to harm
them, but when I told them my goal,
they dared to challenge me.
And they paid the price
for that insupportination.
They were good men, and they all
had families on Angel Island.
Yes, I'm aware.
I suppose I'll have to bury
their families beside them.
You are...
THE DEVIL!
HILL!
5 million, 10 million, 20 million.
Enaru, what should we
do with this old man?
He's pathetic.
He's useless. Can we kill him?
Just throw him into the sea.
I doubt he can even be
used for manual labor.
This shrine, on the other hand,
could be quite useful to us.
But what we really need are the
services of the divine warriors.
They could be put to work in
bringing about my ultimate goal!
They will never help you in your cause.
Silence you're no longer
in charge old man!
20 million volts.
No!
Get away from him!
God does exist in this world.
How mortifying.
And that God is me.
The Devil Fruit.
It's the Rumble Rumble Fruit.
If I'm not mistaken,
this particular fruit is said to
have the power of invincibility.
The power of lightning.
But lightning?
There's no way.
A human has no chance against that.
It is time.
All that I have foreseen
will finally come to be.
The four of you should feel
honored to have survived this long.
Now, come along,
you will join me as I gain passage to
my dream world, to the Endless Birth!
Come with me, come and
fulfill your destinies!
Why would we?
There I will build an
indisputable nation of gods,
where only the Chosen Ones
are permitted to live,
a utopia of boundless and eternal power!
What is he saying?
I will not let those who are unworthy,
like those incompetent subordinates of
mine, sully the stature of this new nation.
Only those who pass my judgment may
bask in the glory of my company.
And what will you do if we refuse?
No, Robin!
Refuse?
But why?
Why refuse to join me?
If you stay here,
you'll fall into a bottomless pit along
with the rest of this unnatural nation.
I have no doubt you could destroy the
entirety of the Upper Yard in one fell swoop.
But if you decide to destroy all this,
then won't you also be destroying
something that you cherish?
Do you mean the Golden Bell?
Yes, that's right.
What's the Golden Bell?
The Golden Bell.
Oh, don't worry. No need.
I've already made arrangements.
Based on what I know about
your travels across Sky Pier,
I believe I know where
the bell is located.
I know what you're thinking, and it
won't be long before I have the bell.
You seem surprised.
Did you really think that you, a mere
human, could ever get the better of me?
How foolish of you.
Robin!
There's nothing I hate more in this
world than a cold, calculating woman.
No!
How dare you?
I do as I please.
You've got skills!
And you are completely out of your mind!
Burn bazooka!
Party!
No way!
How did he manage to
neutralize the bazooka's blast?
Huh.
You still don't get it, do you?
Your energy doesn't even register to me.
I'm more powerful than
you could ever comprehend.
The thunderclap reverberated.
And that only happens when the
air expands at the speed of sound.
That's really powerful.
That amount of power is greater
than anything we can handle.
It's true.
He really is made of lightning.
The time is near.
Prepare yourselves.
Soon those who remain will set off
for the endless birth together.
Do you even understand what
a rare privilege this is?
And why do you assume
we'll come willingly?
Hmm?
I don't give a damn about
your so-called dream world!
Zoro!
Stay away from him!
He's too powerful!
You need a lesson.
Soon your body will know.
The power of God.
I possess a tremendous power that you
puny humans can never hope to overcome.
Can you feel it now?
The despair.
If one loses all hope, it is an
experience not unlike losing one's life.
People fear death above all things.
That's why people
prostrate themselves before
an insurmountable power and beg for mercy.
It is simply the natural order of things.
Beings are meant to bow
before that which they fear.
It's a shame.
You're bound by your instincts.
I can't believe how
incredibly strong he is!
What do you think you're trying to do?
And now, time to die.
Are you familiar with the
Sea Prism Stone, Aniru?
Sea Prism Stone?
That's a stone that can
counteract Devil Fruit powers!
Well then, do your worst, Shandora.
Sea Prism Stone?
It's said to harness the power of
the entire ocean into a single blast!
It's the sea, condensed into solid form!
If anything can overcome the power
of the Devil Fruit, it's the stone!
Die!
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
You're aware of the
consequences, are you not?
Your body will pay a heavy price as well.
Why sacrifice yourself for a
homeland you will never regain?
If I must, I'll die. Gladly.
If it means I can take you with me!
Don't do it!
Reject!
Hold our true ambitions in your
heart and speak not of them.
We are the weavers of history.
Those are the words that were
written on a poneglyph 800 years ago.
Poneglyph? Yes.
And when those who sought to steal
the stone revealed themselves,
the Shandora warriors of the City of
Gold fought bravely to protect it.
Did they succeed?
Yes, they did.
However, the battle took its toll.
A great many warriors died that day.
Those few who survived vowed to
become guardians of the stone.
They kept watch over
the city and the sacred
monoglyph they swore
to defend to the death.
And you say that's the true
story of our ancestors?
But then the island and city of gold
were taken away to Skypiea 400 years ago.
Since then, it's been
under Skypean control.
Our ancestors fought to their
last breath to defend that island.
And then it was taken away!
The Upper Yard.
That is our homeland.
But at the same time,
it alone holds a history that has
disappeared into the darkness of time.
Even though it's under the
control of the Skypeans now,
we must never allow the fire of the
proud city of Shandora to die out.
No way!
He really did it!
Robin!
Gunfall!
It can't be!
He's restarting his own heart!
It's not that people fear God.
Rather, it is God who is fear itself.
What the hell is what this guy?
Wiper, I warned you, did I not?
I warned you of the consequences.
And now look where you are.
How pitiful.
You call yourself a warrior.
Don't address me.
As if you know anything about me.
Eight hundred years ago,
proud Shandora warriors fought
for the fate of this city.
They fought to their death to protect it.
I am a descendant of those warriors.
One day our homeland
was taken away from us.
For four hundred years, we've carried
the great warrior Kalkurus injured pride.
We've sought to return our homeland
to its rightful place for generations.
And now that I've finally made it...
You're standing...
in...
my... way.
I must admit you landed a good blow.
But what a cheap trick
using that sea prism stone
and on top of that using
a reject dial should
Easily kill the ordinary
user but you shot it
twice and you're still
breathing quite impressive
However you're still no match for me
Is that...
a bird?
30 million voltino!
So this has a sea prism stone in it, huh?
And now it's your turn,
swordsmen of the blue sea.
The only choice now is
to kill or be killed.
Keaton!
Zoro!
I don't believe it.
Even Zoro.
Everyone has fallen to him.
How could he?
Unreal.
Even as hurt as he is, he
still intends to fight.
What do you hope to prove?
You're going to die anyway.
Why not make it easy on yourself?
Did you say it's been 400 years?
For all that time,
you and the Shendorians have been
fighting to take back your homeland.
And yet, you are the only warrior
who has managed to make it here.
No wonder this nation will soon fall to
the Blue Sea and be lost for all eternity.
How could he do that?
You're fighting for a lost cause.
Can't you see that you'll
never regain your homeland?
He's unstoppable.
So why get back up?
For my ancestors.
I must confess I was
hoping for a better answer
than that but then again
I doubt you're even!
Completely conscious?
Wiper.
Look out!
Wiper, come here.
What is it?
Since you are a descendant of
the great warrior Kal 'gara,
I feel I must impart this to you.
Not many know the real reason
Kal 'gara wanted to regain the
homeland and why he would stop
at nothing to do so So tell me,
what's the real reason?
You see,
Kal 'gara felt that the
loss of his homeland
was his greatest failure The problem was,
he lost something else
important to him El Thor
Of all who stood before me,
you are the only one left.
I...
Just hear me out.
I want to...
I want to go with you.
I've always wanted to go to endless birth
to your dream world
can I come with you